<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Uncategorized-En on 極度乾燥しなさい3.0</title>
    <link>https://walterinsect.github.io/Superreview_v3.0/categories/uncategorized-en/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Uncategorized-En on 極度乾燥しなさい3.0</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- 0.143.1</generator>
    <language>ja-JP</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://walterinsect.github.io/Superreview_v3.0/categories/uncategorized-en/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Archiving city Project - Part 1</title>
      <link>https://walterinsect.github.io/Superreview_v3.0/posts/2020-02-21-archiving-city-project-part-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://walterinsect.github.io/Superreview_v3.0/posts/2020-02-21-archiving-city-project-part-1/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This is one of the assignments done for the course &lt;em&gt;&amp;ldquo;Interrogating the Archive: Preserving and Interpreting Knowledges of the Past&amp;rdquo;&lt;/em&gt; I took during my Master&amp;rsquo;s. It kinda serves as a trivia of Helsinki&amp;rsquo;s city, and a travel guide for history nerds looking for off-the-beaten-track ways to look at Helsinki. And one of the most enjoyable assignment I did during the 2 years.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Special Thanks to Juhana Aunesluoma (University of Helsinki), Mary Jo Maynes (University of Minnesota), Leslie Morris (University of Minnesota), and Hilde Hoffmann (Ruhr-University Bochum, for hosting the tri-university seminar, and all the fellow students in the course that made the inquiry so much more fun.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Archiving City Project - Part 2</title>
      <link>https://walterinsect.github.io/Superreview_v3.0/posts/2020-02-21-archiving-city-project-part-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://walterinsect.github.io/Superreview_v3.0/posts/2020-02-21-archiving-city-project-part-2/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Part 2 of the Archiving the City Project, which is about Landscape forgotten, but embedded in the cityscape through monuments.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;landscape-forgotten&#34;&gt;Landscape Forgotten&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Often landscape is a product of certain historical forces and authority, but they become invisible, just like other historical memory embedded in physical objects. Especially in city space, the landscape changes rapidly and drastically, often traces of the past becomes invisible. Here I present several &amp;ldquo;forgotten&amp;rdquo; traces of the past that shapes Helsinki&amp;rsquo;s landscape.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sarazanmai Ep.1</title>
      <link>https://walterinsect.github.io/Superreview_v3.0/posts/2019-04-17-sarazanmai-ep-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://walterinsect.github.io/Superreview_v3.0/posts/2019-04-17-sarazanmai-ep-1/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Preliminary reaction to Sarazanmai Ep1. Have not watched Sub, so terms might differ.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Probably what I am seeing here is the privacy=self-defining=what it is to be yourself in the internet age. The desire dimension of Asakusa is basically a motif based on cyberspace, where desires of the users are designed to be enhanced. Before the premier, I thought SNS would come in, and it is probably right, seeing the apps motif and all. Just that it was not the core in the first episode. Probably the next one.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
